[Music]
Good morning and good wishes, I'm
all
promoting and introducing
something about police insurance for people
living in Malaysia.
Is it police insurance? This police is recommended
and maintained in the
[Musik] Union
which is very popular in Malaysia
[Musik]
about
150 for every month
[Applause]
[Music]
and the price is able to choose to
take
all the people living throughout
Malaysia.
You want to take or you want to
use the police. You can
call the telephone number given
below. The telephone number we
provide is held.  and made assignments
by
you can contact him for
[Music]
further conditions and
thank you for your cooperation thank you
[Music]